Hip Hip Poohray!
The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh is a animation,
family, adventure film directed by John Lounsbery.
Whether we’re young or forever young at heart, the Hundred Acre Wood calls
to that place in each of us that still believes in magic.
Join pals Pooh, Piglet, Kanga, Roo, Owl, Rabbit, Tigger and Christopher Robin as
they enjoy their days together and sing their way through adventures.
Winnie the Pooh (voice), played by Sterling Holloway.
Piglet (voice), played by John Fiedler.
Rabbit (voice), played by Junius Matthews.
Tigger (voice), played by Paul Winchell.
Eeyore (voice), played by Ralph Wright.
Gopher (voice), played by Howard Morris.
The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh is a dark ride based upon the 1977 film of
the same name, itself based on the Winnie-the-Pooh books by A.
The attraction exists in slightly different forms at the Magic Kingdom in the Walt Disney
World Resort, Disneyland, Hong Kong Disneyland, and Shanghai Disneyland.
The film explores themes of cartoon, dream sequence,
short compilation, cartoon bear, playful.
The tone is lighthearted.